ad4game.com 2018-11-05

# Ad4Game: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (together with our terms of use, which are available at ad4game.com/terms) governs the manner in which Ad4Game Ireland Limited ( **“Ad4Game”** ) collects, uses, maintains and discloses personal data collected from users of the [ad4game.com](https://ad4game.com/) website (the **“Site”** ) as well as all websites working directly or indirectly with the Ad4Game Network. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ad4Game. Please read this policy carefully to understand the views and practices of Ad4Game regarding your personal data and how Ad4Game will treat it. 

### Personal Data on website

Ad4Game fully respects your right to privacy and will collect personal data from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Personal data that we collect about you may include your name, email address, telephone number, instant messenger, social account, home/office address and bank details. Any personal data which you volunteer to Ad4Game will be treated strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. You may refuse to supply personal data to us, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

### Non-personally identifiable information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to distinguish you from other users of the Site and to enhance your experience when using the Site. Cookies may be placed by your browser on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about your use of the Site. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

### How we use collected information

Ad4Game may collect and use Users personal information (only on the www.ad4game.com website, not other websites where we serve our ads) for the following purposes: 

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. It also helps us to administer the Site for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. 
  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  * _\- Safety_  
As part of our efforts to keep the Site safe and secure. 
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or you may contact us via our Site at [support@ad4game.com](mailto:support@ad4game.com)

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and your browser happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

### Sharing your personal information

We may disclose your personal data to third parties:

  * Where we engage trusted third parties to provide services in connection with the Site or our business, including sending out newsletters or surveys on our behalf. 
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. 
  * If Ad4Game or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets. 
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website terms of use (ad4game.com/terms) and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ad4Game, our customers or others. 

We use the following third parties as data processors for the given reasons. Some of the information you provide will be transferred to them for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms. 

  * Close.io to improve and manage our sales processes ([Privacy Policy](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/87166246), [Terms](https://close.io/tos/)).
  * Intercom to manage Customer communications and perform Customer Relationship Management tasks ([Terms & Policies](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies)).
  * MailChimp as our marketing automation platform ([Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/), [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/)).
  * Zoho for invoicing and billing ([Privacy Policy](https://www.zoho.com/privacy.html), [Terms](https://www.zoho.com/terms.html)).

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 7 and 8 of the Companies Act 2014. 

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our network may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement and to compile non personally identifiable information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

The cookies placed by Ad4Game are for attribution (conversion tracking) and frequency capping only. They automatically expire after 28 days. 

Ad4Game fully complies and adheres to the principles of DAA (Digital Advertising Alliance) / NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) and we simply never store any personal information when showing our ads to any visitors for more than 9 months. 

In order to prevent fraud and attribute clicks and conversions, we may collect certain device information including the following: 

  * Name and properties of mobile applications/websites through which a consumer interacts with the Services; 
  * Country;
  * IP Address;
  * Internet browser user-agent used to access the Services; and
  * Identifier for advertisers (IFA).

### Opt-Out:

**All the data we collect is for fraud prevention and conversions attribution only. We do not use interest-based advertising nor retargeting.**

To opt-out of our collection of information from mobile devices, please visit your device’s settings to set the “Limit Ad Track” or other similar feature on your device. You can also opt-out of our data collection and use through the process we described here  [ “Opt Out”](https://ads.ad4game.com/www/delivery/fc.php?ct=1&script=optOut:opt&key=buTumpozI0l1&out=1&response=redirect&redirect_url=https%3A%2F%2Fad4game.com%2Fopt-out%2Fsuccess). You can also make choices about data collection for certain companies by visiting [http://preferences-mgr.truste.com](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). 

Note that if you opt-out you will still see advertising on your device. In addition, if you reset your device identifier or use a different device you may need to renew your opt-out. 

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16 through the Advertising Services and the Site. 

We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites or our advertising partners. Please check their privacy policies before you submit any personal data to such websites or advertising partners. 

### Your Access and Amendment Rights

You have the right, subject to certain exemptions, to obtain a copy of any personal data which we hold about you (for which we may charge you a small fee of €6.35) and to have inaccuracies in the information corrected and to request that we restrict or block the processing of your personal data. If you wish to avail of any of these rights, please contact our data protection officer at [dataprotection@ad4game.com](mailto:dataprotection@ad4game.com). 

### Changes to this privacy policy

Ad4Game has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

Your continued use of the Site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of and consent to the practices described in this policy and terms of use (ad4game.com/terms). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

### Contacting us

If you have any questions, comments or requests in relation to this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please contact us at:  
6-9 Trinity Street, Dublin 2, Ireland support@ad4game.com

This document was last updated on May 18th 2018.
